mobile-barcodes.com 2014-02-15

# Privacy Policy - Mobile-Barcodes.com

This privacy policy outlines eactly how [Mobile-Barcodes.com](http://www.mobile-barcodes.com/) uses and protects our user information that you may provide when you use our website.

[Mobile-Barcodes.com](http://www.mobile-barcodes.com/) is committed to ensuring that your private information is yours and yours only. If we ask you to provide any specific data when using this website, then please feel reassured that it will only be used with accordance of this privacy statement.

In the future, this privacy policy may change. Please frequently visit this page to be reassured that your are happy with any changes.

## What We Collect?

Mobile-Barcodes.com has access to it's log files, which reveal general information such as your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), your browser, referred agent, the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. This information is used to help us to improve our site design to best match the needs of the visitors.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring your personal inforamtion is secure and private. We have a wide range of processes in place to protect this information and your privacy.

## Cookies

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums or blog.  
You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.

## Links

Within the website, there may be various links to external websites. We try and editorially review each link on a regular basis to ensure that all websites we may refer users to is safe and secure. At times, these websites may change resulting in a poor user experience. We are not responsible for any external websites and cannot be held liable for their contents at any time.

## Advertising

We use various forms of Google Adsense advertising on Mobile-Barcodes. As a result Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. Google makes use of a DART cookie enabling it to serve ads to our user base, depending on their visit to Mobile-Barcodes and other sites on the Internet. If necessary, you can opt out of Google's use of the DART cookie on [Google's ad and content network](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html) privacy policy.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation tonot having this information used by these companies, click here.

### Contact

For more information about ourr privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.mobile-barcodes.com/contact-us/) for a swift answer.
